{
    "subject": "Chris_Rock",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "I_Think_I_Love_My_Wife",
    "human_readable": "Chris Rock directed the film I Think I Love My Wife.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9636899828910828,
            "question": "Has Chris Rock directed any other films besides I Think I Love My Wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9484583735466003,
            "question": "Who directed the film I Think I Love My Wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9411079287528992,
            "question": "What was Chris Rock's role in I Think I Love My Wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.780731737613678,
            "question": "Who starred in I Think I Love My Wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7677829265594482,
            "question": "What is the name of the film Chris Rock directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7676491141319275,
            "question": "What genre is the film I Think I Love My Wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5966163277626038,
            "question": "Where was I Think I Love My Wife filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.514673113822937,
            "question": "What year was I Think I Love My Wife released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4611995220184326,
            "question": "What themes are explored in I Think I Love My Wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4170915186405182,
            "question": "Was I Think I Love My Wife a critical and commercial success?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Rock directed the film I Think I Love My Wife.",
            "html": "yago_22910_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes are explored in I Think I Love My Wife?",
            "html": "yago_22910_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was I Think I Love My Wife released?",
            "html": "yago_22910_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was I Think I Love My Wife filmed?",
            "html": "yago_22910_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22910_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Chris Rock directed the film \"I Think I Love My Wife\". This is stated explicitly in multiple documents, including file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22910/re-ranker-msmarco/50.txt and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_22910/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Chris Rock directed the film \"I Think I Love My Wife.\" For instance, multiple documents mention Chris Rock as both the writer and director of the movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}